

Contact



Warszawa



+48 696 769 767



mateusz1836@gmail.com



mateuszkarpinski.netlify.app



github.com/MattyKarpinski



linkedin.com/in/MattyKarpinski

Education

05.2022 - 06.2022

Product Design Level UP DaftCode, El Passion.

11.2021 - 12.2021

Product Design Beginners DaftCode, El Passion.

2020 - 2021

Białystok University of Technology User Experience Design and web analytics, Postgraduate studies

2018 - 2020

Białystok University of Technology Mnagement and production of engineering, Master degree

09.2018 - 06.2019

Student, Polytechnic Institute of Viana do Castelo, Portugal, Program

2014 - 2018

Białystok University of Technology Mnagement and production of engineering, Engineer degree

07.2017

Student, Summer School, Zhejiang University Ningbo Institute of Technology, China.

Mateusz Karpiński



About me

I try to be a multidisciplinary person because of the particularly wide range of fields that have a direct impact on the construction of digital products, especially their customisation for users. For this reason, I seek knowledge from various fields such as Frontend Development, SEO or User Experience. Maybe one day I will manage to become the proverbial "Unicorn". I'm a very cheerful person, you can always just come to me to talk, not only about your current duties, but also to have a tasty coffee and a joke to make your time more pleasant. I really like to deal with technology related to the construction of computers, new components.



Skills

Programming Stack

- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- React
- Material UI
- NPM
- GIT
- VS Code

User Experience

- Persona creation
 Value proposition canvas
- Customer journey Information architecture
- Business Model Canvas
- Adobe Xd
- Figma
- Adobe Illustrator

Language

- English
- communicative
- French
- basic

SE₀

- GSC
- GA
- Senuto
- Semrush
- Ahrefs
- Screaming Frog
- Analysis of the link profile

Selection of monitored phrases

Building an SEO strategy

Other

- Flexibility and adaptability to a new working environment
- Sense of responsibility for projects
- Attention do detail
- Team work
- Creativity
- Building an SEO strategy



Work Experience

10.2020 - 07.2022

Junior SEO Specialist

WeNet Group S.A.

2022

Web design - Portfolio

(Figma + HTML + CSS + React/ JavaScript) mateuszkarpinski.netlify.app

2022

Web design - Furniture Zone

(Figma + HTML + CSS + React/ JavaScript) furniture-zone.netlify.app

10.2020 - 06.2021

SegreApp mobile app design

Project within the postgraduate studies

09.2017

Intern, AC Spółka Akcyjna, Białystok



Hobbies

Technology / Traveling

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).